var questions = [
  {
    "question":
        "What is one primary advantage of investing in ETFs compared to mutual funds?",
    "answers": [
      "ETFs offer ownership in a single company's stock",
      "ETFs provide the ability to trade throughout the trading day",
      "ETFs are always actively managed by investment professionals",
      "ETFs are only available to institutional investors",
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
  },
  {
    "question": "What management style do most ETFs follow?",
    "answers": [
      "Actively managed",
      "Passively managed",
      "A mix of both active and passive management",
      "ETFs do not follow any particular management style",
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
  },
  {
    "question": "What is one potential risk of investing in ETFs?",
    "answers": [
      "They are not allowed to trade on stock exchanges",
      "The management fees are generally higher than those of mutual funds",
      "They inherently track the index with 100% accuracy",
      "Their performance may differ from the index they aim to replicate",
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3,
  },
  {
    "question": "What can leverage in an ETF potentially do?",
    "answers": [
      "Reduce the complexity and risk of the ETF",
      "Decrease the potential gains and losses",
      "Amplify the potential gains and losses",
      "Make the ETF less attractive to investors",
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "Why are ETFs generally considered more tax-efficient than mutual funds?",
    "answers": [
      "Their dividends are always tax-exempt",
      "Their creation and redemption processes minimize taxable events",
      "They are only taxed on long-term capital gains",
      "They are not subject to the same tax laws as mutual funds",
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "Which type of ETF aims to provide exposure to the entire stock market or significant portions of it?",
    "answers": [
      "Sector ETFs",
      "Broad Market ETFs",
      "Bond ETFs",
      "Commodity ETFs",
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "What type of ETF would you choose if you wanted to invest in stocks of companies outside your home country?",
    "answers": [
      "Bond ETFs",
      "Commodity ETFs",
      "International ETFs",
      "Thematic ETFs",
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "If you believe a particular industry, like healthcare, is going to perform well, which type of ETF might you consider?",
    "answers": [
      "Broad Market ETFs",
      "Bond ETFs",
      "Leveraged ETFs",
      "Sector ETFs",
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "Which type of ETF is more suitable for short-term trading due to its complex strategies involving financial derivatives?",
    "answers": [
      "Broad Market ETFs",
      "Inverse ETFs",
      "Bond ETFs",
      "International ETFs",
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "What does the Vanguard FTSE Developed Markets ETF aim to provide exposure to?",
    "answers": [
      "Developed markets outside the U.S.",
      "Only U.S. large-cap stocks",
      "Emerging markets exclusively",
      "U.S. government bonds",
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "An ETF trades at \$100 per share. An investor buys 200 shares using \$15,000 of their own money and borrows the rest from their broker. If the ETF's price increases to \$120 per share, what is the investor's return on investment (ROI)?",
    "answers": ["33%", "40%", "60%", "80%"],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "An investor shorts 150 shares of a stock priced at \$50 per share, expecting the price to decline. The share price then rises to \$60. How much is the loss?",
    "answers": ["\$1,000", "\$1,500", "\$1,750", "\$2,000"],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "If a leveraged ETF has a 2x leverage ratio, how much does the ETF’s value change if the index it tracks changes by -3%?",
    "answers": ["-3%", "-6%", "-1.5%", "0%"],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "If an ETF has a 1% management fee and an investor has \$20,000 invested in it, how much will they pay in management fees annually?",
    "answers": ["\$200", "\$100", "\$250", "\$150"],
    "correctAnswer": 0,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "An investor wants to invest in an ETF that has a 0.25% expense ratio and tracks the S&P 500. If they invest \$40,000, what will be the annual cost due to the expense ratio?",
    "answers": ["\$40", "\$50", "\$75", "\$100"],
    "correctAnswer": 3,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "If the iShares MSCI Emerging Markets ETF has an annual return of 10% and an investor initially invested \$5,000 in it, what will the investment be worth after one year?",
    "answers": ["\$5,100", "\$5,500", "\$5,750", "\$5,000"],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "An investor purchases 500 shares of the Invesco QQQ Trust (QQQ) at \$350 per share. The ETF’s value increases to \$370 per share. What is the total value of the investor’s holdings now?",
    "answers": ["\$175,000", "\$180,000", "\$185,000", "\$190,000"],
    "correctAnswer": 2,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "If the Vanguard Total Stock Market ETF has an annual return of 8% and an investor initially invested \$10,000 in it, what will the investment be worth after two years?",
    "answers": ["\$11,664", "\$11,000", "\$11,600", "\$12,000"],
    "correctAnswer": 0,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "A broad market ETF has an expense ratio of 0.15%. An investor has \$30,000 invested in the ETF. What will be the annual expense?",
    "answers": ["\$30", "\$45", "\$50", "\$60"],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "An investor owns shares of a commodity ETF worth \$15,000. If the ETF’s value increases by 5%, how much will the investment be worth?",
    "answers": ["\$15,750", "\$16,000", "\$16,250", "\$16,500"],
    "correctAnswer": 0,
  },
];
